Hello, everyone.
Our live broadcast is about to start.
If you haven't joined yet, you'd better hurry up.
Hello, our live broadcast is about to start.
Today, we're going to talk about how to make shoes.
We're going to make a pair of men's shoes.
We're going to share the materials for this live broadcast with you.
If you're interested, you can do it yourself.
Then,
you can refer to our previous live broadcast about self-defined writing and hair.
We're going to make a pair of new shoes for your Cologne model.
First of all, we're going to load our template into it.
Then we load the corresponding model into it.
I made a pair of shoes like this.
In fact, they're from our men's model.
The virtual model is also going to be shared with everyone.
If you're interested in it,
you can also reply the materials and links with the official public account of Cologne and get our related materials.
Okay.
First of all, after we load this template into it,
I'll show you the location where this template needs to be run.
I'm going to give it an open position.
You can see that I'm now opening a horizontal position.
And then I'm going to give it a split line.
And then I'm going to choose the position where the board needs to be symmetrical.
And then I'm going to use our shortcut control plus D,
which is to duplicate the board and the floating line to match it.
And then we're going to move some of the boards back to the 2D window.
Move it to a position that's closer to our virtual model.
And then we're going to click on the 3D window to reset the 2D board.
Put our board in front of our model model.
And then we're going to make a shoe this time.
Then we're going to make a shoe this time.
In the next step, I will select all the other panels in addition to the bottom of the shoe and the side of the shoe, and then save it.
I will share the live material with you this time, because it is particularly difficult to make this shoe panel.
Then we open a physical surface like this, because I need to distinguish the front or the back of my current panel, so that it is convenient for me to deny it.
I use the positioning tool to arrange the bottom of my shoe like this.
You can see that it is in a relatively positive state.
Then, because our panels are relatively small, we can select all the panels first, and then reduce its particle diameter to 5.
Because the size of the panel is relatively small, we can select all the panels and reduce its particle diameter to 5.
When we make the shoes, the bottom of our shoes is very important, because we have to arrange its position well.
So we will look at its position from various angles.
I will rotate it to check the position of the bottom of my shoe.
After that, I just changed it to the opposite side.
I changed it to the front position.
After I adjusted the position of the bottom of my shoe, the bottom of my shoe is connected to the bottom of my foot.
The other side is connected to the ground.
So I will directly cut the outer layer of the board.
You can see that the outer layer of the board can be copied from the current board position.
It is copied in the same direction.
And the position is the same.
This way, we don't need to arrange it again.
Next, we can delete the sewing line of the bottom of the shoe.
Then select this board at the same time.
And remove the joint of the bottom of the shoe.
Because we will make some adjustments to the bottom of the two shoes later.
You can see that we turn to the front to see the effect.
Next, I will sew a pair of shoes.
This is the side of the bottom of the shoe.
The side of the bottom of the shoe is in the front of our foot.
Then it is sewn to the back of the shoe like a circle.
Then we can sew it up with a sewing line.
You can see that I have given two starting and ending points on this board.
We just need to sew them in according to these two points.
Then I found that I sewed the wrong direction on both sides.
I will sew it in a different direction.
Then we sew it together.
In this way, I sew the top of the shoe with the top of the board.
And the bottom of the shoe with the bottom of the board.
Then I sew the bottom of the shoe with the top of the board.
Then we sew the height of the side of the shoe together like this.
In this way, because I have established a sewing relationship with the side of the shoe,
I only need to choose the side of the shoe at the 3D window.
Let me move these two pieces first.
Choose its side.
Add this side directly to the side.
You can see that it is arranged directly.
Then I open the simulation to check its shape.
You can see that this is a shoe base.
Because it consists of three boards.
A top layer, a bottom layer, and a side layer.
In this way, we can simulate the thickness of the real shoe.
There is a little trick here.
In order to make its shape,
the bottom of the shoe and its side can be simulated better.
We can change the folding angle of the sewing line here from 180 degrees to 90 degrees.
In this way, we can form a right-angle sewing angle.
In this way, the effect will be better.
OK.
Open the simulation here.
Next, you can see that the bottom of the shoe is relatively soft on the side.
We need to add a fabric about the bottom of the shoe.
In this way, I will use the physical fabric of Trim Hardware,
which we bring with us in the software.
You can use this fabric directly to load it.
OK. Apply it.
In this way, we can pass through.
Because I have already frozen the upper and lower layers of the shoe base,
we can now move one side of it.
So that the bottom of the shoe can have the effect of sticking to the foot.
You can see that this side will be like a real shoe base.
There is also a height from the front to the back.
The height of the back will be higher.
We can continue to make it by adjusting the shape of the board in the later stage.
Of course, if I want to make the shoe base near the foot is flat,
and the bottom is curved,
then you can freeze the upper part.
Then, the bottom is frozen.
Then we simulate.
You can see that the board is naturally frozen.
It will naturally simulate this shape.
Of course, we are normally flat at the bottom.
The top is curved.
This can match the curvature of our feet.
OK.
In the next step, I will activate this virtual model.
By activating it, it can conflict with our board.
We can adjust the position of our shoe base
to make its bottom more close to our foot base.
After we play this virtual model,
we can see that the shoe base is placed in the position of the foot base.
By activating it,
Then we convert the shoe base.
OK.
We should play it.
After we have finished the virtual model,
we can see that the shoe base is now coincident and aligned.
When we turn the top and bottom of the shoe to the forward,
we should see that the upper and the lower shoes are aligned.
Then the foot will connect the bottom of the shoe with the bottom of the shoe because there is a conflict between the shoe and the bottom of the shoe.
We can rotate the shoe and check its position.
Then we can adjust the height of the bottom of the shoe by adjusting the side of the bottom of the shoe.
I have more curve points, so I use the tool to adjust the curve points.
I use the tool to adjust the curve points.
Adjust the bottom of the shoe like this.
Remember to adjust the entire shoe bottom.
The key is to freeze the shoe.
If the shoe is frozen, the bottom of the shoe will be deformed.
So we have to freeze the shoe.
I adjust the height of the shoe.
If you find that there are more curve points on the side of the bottom of the shoe,
you can also use the tool to adjust the curve points.
Or you can use the tool to adjust the curve points.
You can use the tool to adjust the curve points.
Then the number of curve points will be reduced.
And we can adjust the time here.
After we made the shoe bottom, we can choose it.
choose it, and then freeze it.
In this way, we can start from the bottom of the shoe,
like building a house,
after the base is done,
we will make it layer by layer.
Next, we will take the position of the entire shoe surface,
and remove the stock.
After removing the stock,
we will start to arrange it.
We first take these small boards,
which are shoelaces.
The production of this shoelace
is the same as what I told you before,
the production method of the back of the swimsuit
is the same.
It is the same,
through the small short boards.
I will not take it carefully here.
We select the board like this,
and then use the quick arrangement tool
to arrange it in the corresponding model position.
After you select the board,
you can see that there is a square center
in the upper right corner of the board.
We can select it,
click on the corresponding position of our virtual model,
and we can arrange our board quickly.
Okay, this is a,
let me take a look,
is it on the left side or on the right side?
Let me align it.
First, put it on the right side of our corner.
Then, select the other side,
put it on the left side of our corner,
and rotate it.
Okay, these two sides are the opposite sides.
I now turn it over on the surface,
so that it faces the outside.
In this way,
it is convenient for me to make a,
a partition of the column layer.
Then, next, we choose this is a,
a,
a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a
It will be easier for us to make it.
You can also follow up
Go to your basic version
To do some design
See if you have more ideas
You can design some more cool products
Okay, I'm going to change this background to black
It's easy for you to tell where it's where
I'm going to do a seam on the board
And then?
Because I just turned my board over
So this board is turned over
I'm going to adjust its position again
It's a cross-section of the line
I'm going to rearrange this side board
Turn it over first
And then?
Put it in the right place
This side is on the right side
Move it over
This side is on the left
The advantage of this is that we can sew the board
It's easier
We sew these places together like this
This sewing is relatively simple
So I sewed it faster
You can see that it's basically point by point
I've already adjusted the length of this board
All you have to do is point by point
You can sew it up
Very simple
Okay, this position is a point
That's our diagonal board
It's going to be a little bit bigger
The front is going to be a little bit bigger
And then?
The front is going to be a little bit smaller
It's going to shrink a little bit in there
You can sew it up directly
This is the right side
We sew it up in this position
Okay, so basically
We sewed up all the sewing lines on the front
And then?
That's the bottom of the shoe
The bottom of the shoe
You can take a look at it
We sew the whole bottom of the shoe from the back to the front
We're going to align the back of the shoe first
And then?
From the past
The rest of the position is the same
You can sew it up to one to n
Because the bottom of our shoes on both sides are not linked
So we're going to have to pay attention when we sew it up
Is to sew one side after the other
We're going to sew the other side
Because of the bottom of our shoes
You know
The bottom of our shoes
It's not completely symmetrical on both sides
Because we're going to have some shape on the bottom of the shoes
It fits the shape of our feet
So the two sides can't be linked
Okay, this side
I'm going to sew it up like this
This place seems to be wrong
I'm going to sew it up again
I'm going to put it in the wrong place
I'm going to go around here and sew it up
Our shoe head
The whole shape is sewn up
After the entire shape of the shoe surface is sewn up
We can select the board
Harden it
Then turn on the simulation
You can see that this shoe is put on this foot
Very simple
As long as you put the board in place
Just sew it up
And then?
Let's adjust the shape of this shoe
I'm going to choose the seam line at the bottom of this shoe
Change its seam line to 90 degrees first
Take a look at the effect
Why is this place a little bit
Let's take a look at what's the reason
Well, what about this side
I put this one
I'm going to pour the fabric of this shoe into it
The fabric of the shoe
And then?
I've got two fabrics ready here
You can take a look at me
One fabric?
It's one of us
A gold tail sand
The strength of the gold tail sand is very small
And then his bending strength is very large
This is a piece of fabric
The other piece of fabric is his one
The strength of the gold tail sand is relatively large
The bending strength is also very large
In this case
We can maintain the shape of the whole shoe
Because you know
The front of the shoe is probably made of some cowhide
Or something like this
Hard leather
To do
So our fabric is going to have to be a little bit harder
I'm going to choose these few pieces of fabric
Apply the fabric to it
Let's see which one is harder
This is the front of the shoe
Apply it
And then the head of the shoe
I'm going to apply it to fabric 1
Open the simulation
Let's see what the reason is
Here?
I put the sewing line to him first
Give him this angle
First, give him back to the default one
180 degrees
I'm going to adjust it later
Let's take a look at one of the reasons here
Here, the angle is also to change it back to 180 degrees
Take a look
The back is also
Change them back first
It's better to change it back
It should be the angle I just set wrong
Now let's take a look at it again
What's next
I'm going to put this shoe
The position of the snake
Give him a harder fabric
Because this is soft
Not easy to adjust
Let's put this fabric
The fabric 2 is applied
Give him a little bit of a harder fabric
What's next
Let's put this on the front of the shoe
It also shows you this
The position of the hole in the shoe belt
Let's put this hole in it
Turn it into one of them
Turn it into a base line
Turn it into an inner line
Then turn it into a hole
Let's take a look
Let's choose these round holes
Make it a inner line
And then the position below
This hole is a little bit ugly
Because of the grid above
Causing this line to be not very round
I'm going to delete these
I'm going to copy the round hole on the top
Then copy it one by one
Then this step
When you are operating
You can directly
Don't like me
Just copy one by one
You can do one in advance
Then copy them all
Let's turn it into a hole
What about here
If you encounter such a problem in the future
That is, after you convert the hole
I found your hole
It's not round
It's a square like this
That means the number of straight lines on it is a little bit less
Because our grid is still not very small
So we can add points to it
Make his rounder
A little bit smoother
Then we're going to use this direct dot division tool
Just add a few straight dots for him
that
This step is also when we are operating
pay attention
Add all these points first
Then repeat this one round directly
Ok
What next
Let's make this slung bag
Because we've already done this забts
I think I'll put the fabric of the shoes in
Next?
I select the sliders and unseal the file.
Then I put the sliders in the 3D window
and put them in the corresponding position.
I'll sew it first.
The sewing method of the sliders is very simple.
We just need to sew the edge of the sliders
together with the edge of the hole hole.
Pay attention to the direction of the sewing.
Sew the left side to the left side and the right side to the right side.
Then the right side to the left side.
Sew the right side to the left side.
Check the direction of the sewing.
Why do we need to add these points?
When we sew the shoelace, it will be easier to have these points
We just need to stitch them one by one
Sew this side to this side
And sew this side to this position
Let's take a look at the line of the 3D window
It doesn't seem to be right
Let's back up the one we just sewed
And sew it to the left
Then sew it to the right
After we sew it, we can start the simulation
The shoelace will pull the two sides of the shoelace together with its tension
Here we can see that we can directly put the 5 straight shoelaces above
Select them directly
Then use our Ctrl plus D
And use our shortcut
To copy the line of the shoelace
Then the line of the shoelace will be on the top
We just need to do it once
Let's simulate
This is the position of the shoelace
It's a little hard
Change the shoelace material
Adjust the position
Since the size of the shoelace is done
Open the surface of the
Then check the position of the shoelace
Adjust the length of the shoelace
Adjust the position of the head of the shoelace
I changed it to a material 2
It's a hard material
This way it can stand up
Let me check it again
What's the reason for this place
This is my sewing line
It's 180 plus 9
Because our fabric is out of the way
So our angle should be
Give it 180 plus 9
See this way
It stands up
Then the other positions are the same
Let's adjust the size of the shoelace
Here is 180 plus 9
Is 270
Enter 270
Then simulate it
I just add a little haul
back
Behind the back 90
Anyway the base of the shape
when everyone is doing
You can always use this angle
you can also
أن90
Because some students
During production
This fabric will do it
So this angle is not absolute
During production
In this way
Let's get off the angle
The whole shoes
It's on the side
Let's nun
To the front of the shoes
It's at the shoulders
Then we come to see
This shoelace is a bit long
First, put the shoelace in the 2D window, and shorten the plate a little bit.
Let's adjust the other positions.
Here, when you sew, you can check your sewing line.
When you sew, there may be some small problems.
Here, adjust the position of the sewing line, and so on.
Let's simulate the shoelace a little bit.
When you are making the shoelace,
because we have reduced all the particles to 5.
In fact, the shoelace is smaller.
You can choose it.
Make the shoelace smaller.
The particle diameter of the shoelace is lowered a little bit.
OK.
Next, let's adjust the shape of the shoelace.
First, we choose the position of the back of the shoelace.
Because we want to make the thickness of the side of the shoelace.
Let's see how to make it.
First, I will use the internal line tool.
In the position of the back of the shoelace,
there is a side line.
This is a bit like the inside of our shoes.
Then we cross the line from the top of the shoe.
First, let's adjust the case shape of the shoelace.
Then, let's make the shape
of the one at the very beginning.
Remove the darkening from the front.
Draw another line from here.
This line is similar to the line of the back of the shoe.
It has a thickness.
We draw the inner line here.
Then we close the line.
Now the inner line is drawn.
Set the inner line as an inner border.
Then it will have an airy effect.
You can change the shape here according to your own design.
For example, the shape of the line does not have to be the same as mine.
You can draw some divisions according to your own design.
You can play your own game here.
This is a design ability.
Then we select this version and give it an inner layer.
Here I choose the inner layer of this dragon.
In order to make the back of the shoe have an airy effect on the side.
You can see that I choose its sewing line.
I now default the sewing line type to Tend.
Then we change its sewing line type to Custom Angle.
Then it will be airy like this.
You can see that.
Next, I delete the sewing line first.
After deleting it, we divide it.
In this way, we can set different sewing line angles on each side.
To show our design effect.
We can use Tend for the position near the heel and the side.
Then we use Custom Angle for the position of the upper eye.
Let's sew it first.
Here I adjust it.
You can see that I set the position of the upper eye to Custom Angle.
So you can see that the position of the upper eye of the shoe has a bulging effect.
Because of the tension of the sewing line.
You can see that.
In this way, we have the thickness of the shoe on the side.
If you want to make the thickness of the shoe on the side thicker.
Then you can give the inner layer of the dragon to the inner layer of the dragon.
In this way, you can have a third layer.
In this way, this position will be thicker.
Then the second layer of the shoe will be thicker.
In this way, you can have a third layer of the shoe on the side.
Now I make some like this.
Here I make some like this.
I make some like this.
I choose this inner layer first.
I look at the shape of the line.
I feel that this part is too narrow.
I make it wider.
Then we cut the line.
Adjusting the angle again.
The angle of the front is too big, so I make it a little bit smaller than 180, to make it a little bit flat.
Ok, now we select the board that we just cut.
We make this board to have a cologne layer on the outside.
You can see that it will have a thickness here.
Because you know that we usually have some thicker fabric at the heel.
Of course, there are many shoes that also like to design at the heel.
There is a sound, there is a sound.
Ok, then here, everyone should pay attention.
The board we use at this time, because the fabric I use is relatively hard.
If you use the traditional pressure directly, it may not be able to bend.
What I am using here is an increase in bump, increase in thickness, increase in thickness and bump.
In this case, give it a bump thickness, let it bend a little bit.
Of course, we will continue to carve out this board.
We make another layer for it.
Let it look a little bit thicker.
I first unbend this board in the middle.
Then select the middle position for it.
Select it and merge it together.
Then use the built-in line tool.
Use this hook outline tool to select these boards.
Hook it into a board.
Then I reduce the particle density here a little bit.
We can make an external expansion of the board from this line.
In this way, we will have an extension at the back of the shoe.
This is the design effect.
At this time, I will sew this circle and the upper circle together.
Then sew the bottom circle and the bottom circle together.
Then we adjust its sewing line type.
Add this board to the outside.
Then you can see that there will be a side at this position.
At the back of the shoe, there will be a relatively obvious thickness.
Then apply the fabric at the bottom of the shoe.
I added some gilding at the bottom of the shoe.
Add a little bit of gilding at the top.
Next, we will make the heel of the shoe.
I want to make a surprise egg-shaped,
In the middle, I will add this inner line
to make this expansion sharing effect.
Let's see.
Then apply a gilding at the inner line.
Then determine.
Then add a slash at the middle of the inner line.
It's a little bit too backward, so let's adjust it
Add a new inner line here
So it has a curve, and make a division design here
Then let's adjust the curve of this line
Then let's select the point of the banana
Add a point in the position of the banana
Then cut the point of the banana
It's not easy to select here, let me select it
Pull this line out
Select this point and divide the inner point
Then add another point behind it
Divide this point and delete this line in the middle
In this way, the position of this line is changed
Then combine these two points together
The line behind
I continue to add a new inner line from this point
Here is a division design
Next, I will make a double layer effect on this plate
Here, we use the hook plate first
It's a little inconvenient here
Let's select this plate directly
Let's see how to solve it
Suddenly I remembered a relatively simple method
We don't need to cut out the joint
Here, you can select this plate directly
Then give it a column
Let's make this column layer
After the column layer is made
Let's solve this column layer for it
Then use the hook outline tool
Cut off this inner line
If you cut it off, we can get a complete plate
In this way, it will be easier for us to operate
Let's duplicate the other side
To the outer corner
Choose the inner line
Do it in this way
And then let's copy it
This point is too small
Not easy to select
OK
Then we copy the other side
We add this plate to select it
Add together to outside
OK, simulate
You can see it over here
There will be one
I'll sew the back root here
All right
This is a little bigger
Let's sew the back of the head
As you can see, there is a three-dimensional effect on the side
This side is a bit old, let's see what the reason is
The sewing line here has been sewed, and it has not been checked just now
Let's adjust the shape of the sewing line
Let's sew it again and simulate it
OK, it's OK like this
Next, I want the side root to have a more obvious thickness effect
I choose them and add a thickness of 3.5
At the same time, I will set the edge distance of the panel from 100 to about 20%
In this way, the turning side of the side will be more sharp
It's not as round
As you can see
In this way, we are in the same place
I made such an extension of the bottom of the shoe
I continue to reduce the thickness of the contact
Then I want to add another one on the side
Here, I add another design to the position of the heel
It's more popular in recent years
This is the feeling of a thicker bottom of the shoe
I'll send him a seam line here and cut it off
Then I sew it out
As you can see, it's very simple like this
Here, let's adjust its edge temperature and distance setting
In this way, you can see that the bottom of the shoe will have some design effects
The side of the shoe, the side of the heel, the side of the bottom of the shoe
In this way, the heel of the shoe
And then the heel of the shoe
I'll adjust its thickness a little bit
I'll add a thickness to it
The heel of the shoe, I'll freeze it a little bit
If you want to make your own shoes
With your clothes
You can make a pair of shoes according to the teacher's teaching
Then go to see us
There was a video called
A self-defined hair
Live
That one will teach you how to do this
Our UBJ file is made into this
Can be customized into our system
System-use files
This will be more convenient
Okay, next, let's do the bottom of the shoe
Everyone knows that there may be some of these anti-slip patterns on our shoes, right?
Let's take a look at how to do anti-slip patterns
In fact, it's very simple
We can draw an inner line on the bottom of the shoe
Then set it up for him to make an inner line
And then you can set the width of each of your anti-slip layers
This one I made this anti-slip pattern
It's a little bit like we have some slits
It's very, very three-dimensional under it
Then set the width to five
Then expand the number to increase
Let's increase it to 30
Then I'm in this position
I'm going to use one of our circular tools
Give him an inner circle
Draw an inner circle here
Then from the basis of this inner circle
Give him an inner line
Let's try it
See if you can do some of this from this inner circle
Effective
Okay, build a point in the position of the banana on the board
Then break this point
Delete the useless position outside
Then go from this line to the inner line
Then everyone can see
In this case
If you feel that this line is not perfectly drawn
You can also draw by hand
Then we can come
Set its expansion number
As well as the expansion interval of our board
You can also choose to extend or not
This number is a little high
Let's lower this number a little bit
Let's see how much is appropriate
Here I changed to a 20
In this way
From the first line
Expanded it
Such a row of inner lines
We need to put these inner lines
The position of the banana below us
Give him a point in the position of the corner
Then it is convenient to cut it off
I am now choosing these
The position of the banana below
Then right-click on this line
Choose to align
To the point of increase in the inner line
Then select these points
Select the points to be established
Divide it
Then delete the unnecessary below
Then delete this pair of points
OK
Then here we wait
Direct
After you draw this line
Direct to it
Then right-click
Give him a outer layer
Then the outer of the dragon
Then the outside of the dragon
It should be the inner layer of the dragon
The inner layer of the dragon
So we need to create an inner layer, and then move it to the other side to simulate it.
Next, we need to remove this panel and move it to the other side.
At the same time, we need to select all the excess lines and cut them off.
Then we need to select the parts that are not needed and delete them.
So now we need to separate them one by one.
Let's select them one by one and delete them one by one.
Delete the excess panels.
The same goes for the bottom part.
We can select the bottom part and separate it one by one.
Let's check it out.
Select one panel.
Then separate it one by one and delete it one by one.
Next, we need to use the sewing machine.
We need to use the sewing machine.
We need to sew it back to its original position.
It's very simple.
Of course, if you think it's a bit troublesome to sew the bottom part,
you don't have to do it.
I just want to make it more realistic.
This side is wrong.
Let's change it a little bit.
This side is also sewn up like this.
But this side, because we are in the middle, we are all broken points.
Let's sew it with free sewing.
It feels like free sewing is not very convenient.
Is there a better way?
We can convert all our black straight lines into curve points.
In this way, our panel is a whole root.
It will be easier to sew with a straight line.
Let's select all these points.
Then convert it into a free curve point.
The following position is also selected.
Then select it, select it, select it, right-click, convert it to a free curve point.
The above position is also.
Of course, this step can also be done before you cross the dragon layer.
We select it like this, select it, select it, right-click, convert it to a free curve point.
Of course, the original inner line of our bottom line also needs to be converted to a free curve point.
The advantage of this is that we can use the sewing machine directly.
Because it is a whole piece.
It will be easier to sew a whole piece of straight weight.
If you feel that the process of converting the free curve point is very long,
you can also sew it one by one.
This is all possible.
After we convert it like this, we can sew it directly with a line.
You can see that you can arrange it one by one.
It's very simple.
Let's see the result.
This side is wrong.
OK, let's simulate this.
There seems to be some problem.
Let me have a look.
We want to increase the thickness of the pattern at the bottom of the shoe.
I directly select the lines we just sewed, and then increase the thickness of the curve.
Then you can see that after increasing the thickness of the curve, it is very thick.
Let's adjust its bending rate.
In this case, we will adjust it from 100 to 20.
This edge will be sharper.
As you can see, the bottom of the shoe is as real as the bottom of the shoe.
We sew it on our shoes.
After we have finished the bottom of the shoe, we can do the design on the shoe surface.
First, let's take a look at the position of the strap.
First, let's make a cut in the position of the tongue.
Then select it and make a cut line and sew it.
Then cut the dragon layer.
Then let's change the fabric.
Now let's adjust the type of the stitch line.
Let it bulge.
The fabric is probably too hard.
Let's change it a little bit.
Then let's do the same thing.
As you can see here, it will bulge like a real shoe.
We can adjust the angle of the sewing line to make the effect of bulging weaker.
Now let's layer the side of the shoe.
We can also change the shape of the sewing line to make it bulge.
Now let's look at the side of the shoe.
First, let's select the two basic lines and make them into an inner line.
Then we can make a border line from the base of the inner line.
Here, we change the number of compartments to 2 and adjust the opposite direction.
Then set the border line.
Here, we set the border line to 8.
Here, because I want to set two different border lines,
we can change the border line from all to single.
This is also a new function of our previous model.
Let's adjust the first line.
The distance of the first line is 5 mm.
Now adjust it to 8.
Then adjust the width of the second line to 7.
Adjust it to 8.
Click OK.
You can see that we can adjust the width of the first line to 7.
Head down and click methods.
You can see here that this interface installer is very convenient.
Here, you can face your bare foot or you can also face your pre-used shoe.
You can adjust both widths or both meantime and time USE the armrest.
Here, I'm going to show you how to change the width,
so just make sure your bottom left button isれない
Position it ages.
This place has a sharp corner due to the strength of the sewing line.
I delete the sewing line here and sew it again on both sides.
Because the angles of each place are different, if they are all set to Katsuma, they will all bend.
Divide it into pieces and sew it again.
As long as you keep Katsuma Angle in the upper eye.
Turn it over like this.
You can give it a fixed point here.
Turn it over and give it a fixed point here.
It's a little unstable here.
I choose to add it to the inside and simulate it again.
You can see that we have basically made the shape of a shoe.
Let's go down and do the details.
There are two air holes on the side of the shoe.
We hook it into the internal shape and convert it into a hole.
I'm going to do some design here.
So I choose this edge.
Let's see how to design it.
Let's select this edge first.
Give it an internal line.
Then draw a root.
Then to that 3 mm.
2 mm.
Then we use the hook outline tool to select these edges from this base.
Hook it into an internal shape.
Then hook it into a board.
Let's sew this board up.
The purpose of this is that I want to get a board that is a little shorter than the original bottom board.
In this case, we will use the fabric later.
After using the fabric, it can penetrate the bottom color of the inside through the reserved position.
This will have a color-catching effect.
Okay, let's sew it up.
Then the lower eye is also sewn up.
Then what about the following?
We want to change the type of sewing line.
This side is changed to a Tend.
Then we sew it up and add it to the outside.
On both sides, we change the particle diameter.
This side is relatively large and changed to 5.
Okay.
Then we sew the hole position.
If you are interested in the position of this hole,
you can add a button here to make an iron eye effect.
Change the type of sewing line.
Okay.
Then we connect the two sides of this side.
Give it to this side directly.
Ctrl D.
Also Ctrl D.
Copy it to the outside.
Next, we select this side.
If you give it a side, you can select it.
Use the fabric at the bottom of the shoe.
Because I like the sharpness of the bottom of the shoe.
Then select this plate at the same time.
Give it a rendering thickness.
Make it a little more three-dimensional.
Adjust the curve setting.
It's the same as the previous operation.
Then you can see this.
Then we will have such a side from the side.
The effect of the side protrusion.
This thickness is a little big.
I select it and reduce its thickness a little bit.
Can be adjusted to a 2.5.
2.5.
This thickness is OK.
Okay.
Next, let's do this.
Let's take a look at how to do this.
First, let's do the side of the shoe.
There are two divisions here.
Let's put this division line.
Let's connect it to a plate.
Like the side of our shoe just now.
Sew it out.
After connecting it.
Let's just adjust its particle thickness.
And then use the sewing tool to sew them back.
Actually, we are all based on this.
Some design to do on the original version.
So this version can give you a lot of extension space
You can change the version according to your preferences or design
Then we select this version and add it to the outside
Here we also use the material at the bottom of the shoe
I will increase the thickness of this material
Adjust its edge frequency setting
On the other side, we also select these two lines
Then copy it to Ctrl D
I choose a root here
Do a different design on the inside
There is only one side on the inside
Next, let's take a look at the inside
The thickness of the inner layer is reduced to 1.5
Next, let's make the position of the head of the shoe
Let's get rid of all these panels
Then from the base of our panel
Make an internal line frame
Let's make it an internal line frame
One root is enough
Then set it to 3
Then we
Let's take a look at 2
Then we directly use the hook and loop tool
The selected internal line is cloned into a panel
Sew it up
Add it to the outside
Let's try
Okay, the particle diameter of the panel here is relatively low
I will reduce it a little bit
Like this
OK
Here we are
We finished the central line
Now we can add a vertical line
OK
All of them are adjusted to the edge frequency setting
Then come next
Let's take a look at the slanted surface
The flat surface where the line is already painted
We adjust this shape first
There is a base line on the edge, so we select it directly and convert it to the inner line.
Then we make a cologne layer from this base.
I will show you the effect of the cologne version.
I need to make a seam here.
Make a seam here.
The same on the other side.
Here, because the angle of the human body is shaped,
the angle of the human body is shaped,
we need to adjust the angle of the human body.
Actually, when we make shoes, we will use a shoe string.
The shoe string has a more regular angle.
The angle of the human body will be higher or lower.
So we need to manually adjust the position of the shoe head with a fixing needle.
You can use a fixing needle to adjust the position of the shoe head slowly.
Let us essent for today.
Today we already released the feature in our wechat public account.
Let us instance the feature on the wechat public account and leave messages.
Make sure to leave a comment on the wechat public account.
There should be a corresponding material given to you in the public number to reply to the link, and you can get today's course material, and you can do it right away after you have learned it.
Okay, let's adjust it here.
This material is a little hard. I just deleted all the fixed needles here, so I loosened it here, and I pulled it back and added a fixed needle again.
Okay, I'll just give him a few of these fixed needles at an angle, and then I'll use the positioning tool to adjust its shape.
If you want to use the shortcut and the fixed needle, you can put the mouse on the board and press the W key directly on the board, and then you can quickly add needles.
You don't need to use the fixed needle tool anymore.
We can adjust it as we like.
Let's adjust the fixed point here and delete it a little bit.
When you want to adjust it, you need to slow down a little bit.
Let's take a look at it separately.
In this way, you can see that the slope is rounder.
Let's freeze the slope first.
Then let's take a look at the slope.
The slope is a little thin.
We choose the slope and increase the thickness of the slope.
Let's add a 2 first.
It seems to be a little thick.
Let's choose it again and change its 2 to 1.
OK.
It's more comfortable to look at the slope like this.
Then let's adjust the slope of the slope.
OK.
You can see that in this way,
80% of the whole of a slope has been done.
You can see that the slope of this slope
has a front and a side effect.
Then the next step is to add some fabric to our shoes.
Then we make some color matching.
Now we hide all these basic lines,
internal lines, and fixed needles.
Then don't prevent us from matching the color.
Let's copy a piece of fabric to the bottom of the shoe.
Then I make a color matching for it.
In this case,
I set the color of the fabric to gray.
The theme of my new year this time
is a gray-red color matching.
Let's take a look at the bottom of the shoe.
OK.
Then let's copy another piece
and use a red color for the other one.
This time,
let's copy a brown color like this.
OK.
Then we add a gray color to the bottom of the shoe.
Next,
let's adjust the color of the other places.
For example,
I change the color of my front to gray.
Gray.
Then I use a fabric here.
I use a leather fabric.
That's wrong.
I use leather fabric.
Then I adjust the surface rust can and the reflection strength
to make it have some different appearance.
to give the surface some shine.
Then, we apply the material to the shoe head
and adjust its color to match the color.
I choose a gray color for this side.
The color is a bit heavy.
Adjust it a little bit.
I feel that the shoe head is covered
by the white color at the bottom.
I'm going to untangle it
and cut it off.
After cutting it off,
I'll sew it back together.
Let's simulate it.
Then, we can show the white circle at the bottom.
It will look better.
Adjust the color a little bit.
Click OK.
This one.
The color is not good.
Let's change it.
Make it lighter.
Make it lighter, too.
It will enhance the color contrast.
Here, we can draw a rectangular board
at the back of the shoe.
We can draw a rope at the back of the shoe.
This rope.
This is very simple.
We draw a rectangular board.
Then, we can use a piece of this kind of needle material.
I use this shoelace material directly.
Then, we sew it back.
Sew it to this position.
After sewing it,
change the sewing line type
to this Katsuma Angle.
Remember, this board is relatively small.
So, we need to adjust its particle diameter.
Let's simulate it.
You can see that this board is relatively small.
The particle diameter is relatively large.
So, we need to reduce it to 5.
Then, you can adjust it.
Then, you can adjust it according to the board you drew.
Then, you can adjust it in time.
For example, it seems to be a little short.
Let's take a look at it.
OK.
Then, make this board a little longer.
Then, simulate it.
Then, it's OK.
OK.
Next, we will add some contrast decorations to our shoes.
Here, I also use a red contrast.
It will protect the bottom of our shoes.
It will keep it unified.
In this way, there will be a color match.
You can see it.
Let's adjust the thickness of this thread.
I used a single line 120 here.
Then, we will add another position to it.
We are done.
We will pause it again.
Let's see it again.
Alright.
OK, we adjust the position of our hand.
Adjust it slightly like this.
We see that the torsional η becomes a little57 of one.
And then, adjust theasil iament.
Next, set a minimum value and two points above it.
We can see that we will need more tools.
To adjust this position,
You can also move the list.
Now we will activate the number class.
If we third try to add something,
It will show a little problem here.
Next,
Add a little bit of thickness to the side.
Look at the front and middle position.
Add a little bit of texture to the side of the belt.
Use the grid tool to drag it out.
It's a little bit difficult to simulate.
This version is too small.
Next, add a texture to the belt.
Open the belt and add a texture.
The texture is the logo of our colo.
Use a piece of new fabric for the snake.
Turn off the texture a little bit.
I only need the front side.
Look at the print.
Press the texture.
Finally, we use a flower pattern.
I used a new year's tiger's head.
Because this year is the year of the tiger, so I used a paper-cutting design to put it on the side of the tiger to wish everyone a happy new year.
Our new year is about to start again, so I used a tiger draft to make it have some dark lines on our writing, and it also has the effect of a tiger pattern.
You can search online for these flower draft materials, or you can draw them yourself.
You can see the effect here, and I'm going to match the pattern here, and the side is relatively monotonous, so I'm going to copy this flower draft to the side and make it a dark pattern.
It looks a little better, so I'll use a white color on the other side, and I'll copy it over, and then we'll adjust it again.
And then the front and the front of the flower draft is a little too strong.
It's a little bit too strong. It's a little bit too strong. It's a little bit too strong. It's a little bit too strong.
It's a little bit too strong. It's a little bit too strong.
I'll delete the blind. I don't need this.
In this case, we'll put the flower draft of this shoe in like this.
We're going to take a look at its size again.
The other places?
Adjust a piece and enlarge it here.
good
A little bit bigger here.
Make a piece.
Make a piece, make a piece.
good
After that, we will make a pair of shoes like this
After that, let's take a look
We can select all the shoes
After selecting, directly give it ctrl c and ctrl i
Then copy the whole shoe to another one
Our flower draft is not provided
Because this flower draft can be searched online
You can search Hunian
Flower draft
Hunian paper
You can search a lot
Then copy it out
Then we change one to two
You have to pay attention here
If you want to change the shoes we designed into our models
You can refer to the live broadcast of our previous self-designed shoes
You can make our shoes
By exporting the whole selection as an obj
Then according to
The live broadcast of the self-designed shoes
The live content of the self-designed shoes
Define our shoes into shoes that can also be used by clock
In this way
We will make this shoe for everyone
Then what about the following
We have an answer time
If you have any questions
We can do an answer
What about us here
After the shoes are done
We can directly
In this software
Use one of our rendering engines
Render
Because every time we render here
There will be a little lag
So I rendered it in advance
This is our final rendering effect
You can see here
This is the final rendering effect
For everyone
What about the following
It's a few shoes that we often broadcast
Then what about the above
It's one of our separators
If you are interested
You can take this material yourself
Practice by yourself
OK
What about us today
The live broadcast is over
Then what about the following
If you have any questions
You can take a look together
If you say
Your foot size has become larger
Do you want to re-adjust the size of the shoes
Because in our software
The foot of the model in our software
Is fixed
Whether you are a big model or a small model
Its feet and head are fixed
So you don't need to adjust
If you need to adjust the size
The teacher recommends that you
You can select the whole model for him
Select the whole model
What to do after selecting
We can directly export the file
Export to an OBJ selected
In this case
After we export to an OBJ
You can import it back
He is one
You can directly adjust the size of the model
It's relatively simple
Then how to cut the foot from the model
How to cut the foot from the model
Because this needs to be used
The third-party tool
Is that we directly
The model of Kolo
For example, Maya
Or Zbrush
Or this
This
3D Max
And this
CCD
All right
He can cut the grid
Cut it down
Of course
The foot of this model
The teacher has already shared it with everyone
You don't need to
You can cut it yourself
If you feel that this foot is not good
You can also use other models
To make shoes
All right
How to do the sole
You're late
You can wait for us
A live broadcast next week
In fact, the production of the sole
It's relatively simple
You just put this sole
Arrange it in our feet
The bottom position is fine
And then
The side panel
Sew it up
You can see this
The side panel
Sew it up
It's empty in the middle
You sew this up
After that
The sole is directly simulated
You can take this material directly
Just practice it
And then you have to pay attention
This shoe head
The middle is in the front
Don't sew it back
Don't sew your this
To the back
This is to pay attention
When you go to the show
How do you deal with the strings on the bottom of the clothes
The strings on the bottom of the clothes
well
How do you deal with the strings when going to the show
Belarus where
it says
A lot of
You can use this
Stuck
If the strings are quite a lot
You can use this
Stuck
Just use this false needle
Get it to your clothes
It's best to stick them together
This one
We are on a UE show
The teacher in the live broadcast
It's interesting
magnifying different situations
You can have a look
sor corner
The realmente
Do not
See
In the bottom left corner of our screen, there is our official official account.
You can scan the code directly and then leave a message in the background to get a copy of today's course.
This version is actually quite difficult to play.
The teacher also played for a long time before it came out, so if you are interested, you must collect it.
Where can I download other tutorials?
It's best to search online to see if there is any relevant material.
The teacher here also used a real foot.
If you have the conditions, you can use a foot line to make it look better.
Or if you don't have a friend who makes shoes, can you provide some shoes for you?
The slenderness of this shoe, the slenderness of this shoe,
the slenderness of this shoe,
is that we put this shoe on the cologne layer.
Then you put its sewing line type, see?
Just change the folding angle of its sewing line.
Adjust its folding angle, it will have this effect of bulging.
OK, if everyone has no questions, our live broadcast today is over.
Then give everyone two minutes.
May the whipping fear cafe cheer you?
Yes.
So long.
Bye-bye.
Till you.
From today's program,
everybody be concentrating in speaking kaum.
OK, good work.
OK, bye-bye.
So we have finished,
so I will introduce Lino to the main stage.
A girl will follow,
lonely,
lonely.
So everybody be attentive to Lino's movement.
HIS object is beautiful.
That's all for today. See you next time.